

Husein Putra Widya Pratama

Software Engineer

# **Contact**



+62 821 2707-4919



huseinputrawp@gmail.com



Cisarua, Bogor, Jawa Barat.

## **About Me**

I'm Husein, a software engineer with lots of experience in different industries, mainly focusing on backend engineering. What I enjoy most about being a software engineer is constantly learning new technologies, connecting with different people, and broadening my perspectives. It's what keeps me excited about this journey.

## **Education**

Software Engineering SMK Wikrama Bogor 2016 - 2019

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science | Information System 2020 - 2024

Universitas Binaniaga Indonesia - GPA: 3.54 / 4.00

# **Experience**

#### IT Full Stack Developer

PT Lattice Teknologi Mandiri

Jul 2018 - Dec 2018

· Develop and Maintenance Application

#### IT Staff - Programmer

PT Rembon Karya Digital

Jul 2019 - Jan 2022

- Develop web or desktop-based applications, including internal applications and websites, for clients using PHP Laravel/ CI & .NET Core.
- · Develop Microservice

#### Backend Programmer

PT Web Architect Technology

Jan 2022 - August 2024

- Developed web-based applications, including ecommerce and company profile websites.
- Utilized MySQL DB for data storage and retrieval, ensuring efficient and reliable performance.

## Skills

Programming Languages

HTML | CSS | Javascript | Typescript | PHP | .NET | Node Js | Laravel | Codeigniter | Vue | TailwindCSS | Nest | React | JWT

Others

Microsoft Office | Photoshop | Adobe Premier | Adobe After Effect

# Other Information

Check out my portfolio at site seinovation.my.id.